Do you play?
Palm Swings is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Sean Hoessli.
After moving to Palm Springs, a young married couple puts their love to the
test when they discover that their neighbors are swingers.
Allison Hughes, played by Sugar Lyn Beard.
Mark Hughes, played by Jackson Davis.
Ms. Cherry Bomb, played by Tia Carrere.
Claire, played by Diane Farr.
Jim, played by Chaka Forman.
Lance, played by Jason Lewis.
Dorothy Jacqueline Keely (March 9, 1928 – December 16, 2017), professionally known as Keely Smith, was an American jazz and popular music
singer, who performed and recorded extensively in the 1950s with then-husband Louis Prima, and throughout the 1960s as a solo artist.
Smith married Prima in 1953.
The couple were stars throughout the entertainment business, including stage,
television, motion pictures, hit records, and cabaret acts.
They won a Grammy in 1959, its inaugural year, for their smash hit, "That
Old Black Magic", which remained on the charts for 18 weeks.
The film explores themes of lifestyle, orgy, group sex, palm springs, swinger.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.